<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Asia on Transgender University Guidance</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/</link><description>Recent content in Asia on Transgender University Guidance</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singapore</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/singapore/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="singapore">
 Singapore
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#singapore">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Singapore is an island nation located in Southeast Asia and is known as the financial center of Asia. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s major industries include finance, aviation, technology, pharmaceuticals, and business services. Singapore is home to Chinese, Indian, Malay and other ethnic groups. The official language is English, but most people also speak Chinese, Malay or Hindi.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s level of acceptance towards the LGBTQA+ community is not considered high. It was only in mid-2022 that Singapore decriminalized male same-sex sexual activity, while reaffirming in parliament that marriage is a relationship between a man and a woman to avoid any challenges in that regard. The authorities also impose restrictions on the promotion of LGBTQA+ content, and public attitudes tend to lean towards conservatism. From certain perspectives, Singapore may appear to be legally open but still operates in a conservative manner in everyday life. &lt;sup id="fnref:1">&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1&lt;/a>&lt;/sup>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Japan</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/japan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/japan/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="japan">
 Japan
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#japan">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;blockquote class="book-hint info">
 &lt;p>&lt;strong>Content timeliness and accuracy remain to be seen&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Written by a contributor who is not a long-time resident of Japan, please find out more information from more sources.&lt;/p>

&lt;/blockquote>

&lt;p>Japanese society is built on a household registration structure, and thus transgenders who want to be recognized by society need to be able to have the conditions to obtain a wife/husband, i.e., they need to pass the external appearance, etc., in order to change their documents; and from a cultural perspective, they need to have the will to marry and have children. In addition, the overall social pressure in East Asia is relatively high, the whole social construction is also relatively traditional, and society on 
 &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Recognition_of_same-sex_unions_in_Japan">same-sex marriage&lt;/a> attitudes vary widely.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>China</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/china/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/china/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="china">
 China
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#china">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;blockquote class="book-hint warning">
 &lt;strong>The overwhelming number of negative comments given by transgenders in this country, which may reflect a dangerous environment for transgenders in China.&lt;/strong>
&lt;/blockquote>

&lt;p>Even as a non-Chinese transgender, the society&amp;rsquo;s attitude towards you may still be bad in China, and you may still encounter many problems.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As a transgender exchange or degree student studying in China, you may still face significant difficulties, including but not limited to difficulty obtaining medication through official channels, only a small number of doctor doctors can prescribe a diagnosis of &amp;ldquo;易性症&amp;rdquo; (gender incongruence, but China uses an outdated name) that allows for more medical possibilities &lt;sup id="fnref:1">&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1&lt;/a>&lt;/sup>, very limited doctors who can prescribe HRT/GAHT &lt;sup id="fnref:2">&lt;a href="#fn:2" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">2&lt;/a>&lt;/sup>, lack of psychological support, widespread public attacks and institutional discrimination, and obstruction in academics and employment.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>