<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Transgender University Guidance</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/</link><description>Recent content on Transgender University Guidance</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://uniguide.transacademic.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Managing Energy During the Application Process</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/posts/energy-management/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/posts/energy-management/</guid><description>&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s a common initial thought — at the start of the application process, I tend to see it as a sprint. With just fifty meters left to the finish line, a final push seems enough to get through it. By this stage, language proficiency is secured, background experiences are in place, and many with the urge to study abroad view their desired destinations as lands of opportunity, thinking what&amp;rsquo;s left is just the result, right?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Australia</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/oceania/australia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/oceania/australia/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="australia">
 Australia
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#australia">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="essential-tools">
 Essential Tools
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#essential-tools">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In Australia, this website 
 &lt;a href="https://www.transhub.org.au/">transhub.org.au&lt;/a> provides a wealth of information. The trans-friendly list on it might not be updated timely. Therefore, it&amp;rsquo;s suggested to visit 
 &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/transgenderau/">r/transgenderau - Reddit&lt;/a> to see discussions and gather more information.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="transgender-medical-resources">
 Transgender Medical Resources
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#transgender-medical-resources">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In Australia, adults can proceed with informed consent to access Hormone Replacement Therapy (HRT) / Gender Affirming Hormone Treatment. Specifically, you can contact a local qualified doctor. Some school physicians might be eligible, but if not, they will refer you elsewhere, which might lead to some delay. The speed of obtaining hormones partly depends on the doctor&amp;rsquo;s approachability. In faster cases, medications can be prescribed within two to three weeks. Additionally, these doctors mainly prescribe hormones and antagonists, but they might not be very knowledgeable about gender confirmation surgeries, so they might not provide expert advice.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Computer Science and Technology</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/computer-science/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/computer-science/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="computer-science-and-technology">
 Computer Science and Technology
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#computer-science-and-technology">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="courses-and-materials">
 Courses and materials
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#courses-and-materials">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>
 &lt;a href="https://csdiy.wiki/en/">CSDIY.wiki&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="contests">
 Contests
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#contests">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="algorithm-competitions">
 Algorithm competitions
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#algorithm-competitions">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Algorithm competitions require the design of algorithms to solve mathematically biased problems and receive time and language constraints.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="program-development-competitions">
 Program development competitions
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#program-development-competitions">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Compared to algorithm competitions, program development competitions are a bit longer. It is also not too restrictive on the developer&amp;rsquo;s technology stack, and the questions cover a wide range of aspects, so you can often find a topic that is relatively more suitable for you, and thus more flexible, but often less recognized than program development competitions.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Singapore</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/singapore/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="singapore">
 Singapore
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#singapore">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Singapore is an island nation located in Southeast Asia and is known as the financial center of Asia. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s major industries include finance, aviation, technology, pharmaceuticals, and business services. Singapore is home to Chinese, Indian, Malay and other ethnic groups. The official language is English, but most people also speak Chinese, Malay or Hindi.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s level of acceptance towards the LGBTQA+ community is not considered high. It was only in mid-2022 that Singapore decriminalized male same-sex sexual activity, while reaffirming in parliament that marriage is a relationship between a man and a woman to avoid any challenges in that regard. The authorities also impose restrictions on the promotion of LGBTQA+ content, and public attitudes tend to lean towards conservatism. From certain perspectives, Singapore may appear to be legally open but still operates in a conservative manner in everyday life. &lt;sup id="fnref:1">&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1&lt;/a>&lt;/sup>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Sweden</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/nordic/sweden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/nordic/sweden/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="sweden">
 Sweden
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#sweden">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="transgender-health-resources">
 Transgender Health Resources
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#transgender-health-resources">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In 2022, Sweden prohibits the provision of any hormone and hormone blockers to humans under the age of 18 for non-research purposes. Access to gender-affirming treatment is subject to psychiatric evaluation and must be lived for one year &lt;strong>without any medical help&lt;/strong> to identify with the same gender. &lt;sup id="fnref:1">&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1&lt;/a>&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As of February 1, 2023, Sweden is the only one of the five Nordic countries that has not passed the gender self-identification act.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>United Kingdom</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/uk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/uk/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="united-kingdom">
 United Kingdom
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#united-kingdom">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;blockquote class="book-hint warning">
 &lt;strong>The UK government has blacklisted over 50 countries for &amp;lsquo;making it too easy to change gender&amp;rsquo;, requiring any individual who moves from these blacklisted countries to the UK to reapply for a gender change in the UK. The blacklist includes countries like New Zealand and Belgium that recognize gender based on &amp;lsquo;self-declaration&amp;rsquo;. Please be aware of this condition when applying.&lt;/strong> [^1]
&lt;/blockquote>

&lt;h2 id="visa">
 Visa
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#visa">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The UK offers a work visa policy: if you graduate from a top 50 university in the world in your year of study, you will be eligible for a n-year work visa. So, if you graduated from a top 50 school in the world and you are not satisfied with a local career, you can take note of this information.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>United States of America</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/north-america/usa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/north-america/usa/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="united-states-of-america">
 United States of America
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#united-states-of-america">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;blockquote class="book-hint warning">
 &lt;strong>The overwhelming number of negative comments given by transgenders in some states of this country, which may reflect a dangerous environment for transgenders in some states.&lt;/strong>
&lt;/blockquote>

&lt;p>The United States of America is currently the world&amp;rsquo;s leading country in science and technology and offers a relatively sophisticated system in many areas, including education and employment. Although the law prohibits discrimination against transgenders, transgenders are still treated unfairly in many ways, such as prejudice, violence, harassment, and some local laws.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Austria</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/central-europe/austria/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/central-europe/austria/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="austria">
 Austria
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#austria">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="transgender-related-resources">
 Transgender-related resources
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#transgender-related-resources">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="organizations-and-institutions">
 Organizations and institutions
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#organizations-and-institutions">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
 &lt;a href="https://queerbase.at/">Queer Base&lt;/a> is an Austrian LGBTQ refugee organization aimed at providing shelter, support, and resources for LGBTQ refugees, as well as promoting the protection and advocacy of LGBTQ refugee rights.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="transgender-medical-care">
 Transgender Medical Care
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#transgender-medical-care">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>
 &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/asktransgender/comments/owa7lf/german_transgender_articles_situation_with_trans/?sort=confidence">Questioning transgender medical care in German-speaking regions&lt;/a> &lt;sup id="fnref:1">&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1&lt;/a>&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="learning">
 Learning
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#learning">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>
 &lt;a href="https://studyinaustria.at/en/useful-tips/first-steps#c14974">First Steps to Studying in Austria&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
 &lt;a href="https://oead.at/en/to-austria/entry-and-residence/">Details on visa application requirements and more&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
 &lt;a href="https://oead.at/en/to-austria/entry-and-residence/residence-permit-student-no-mobility-programme">Third Country| Students with letter of admission| No mobility program | No agreement with higher education institution| Residence permit for students staying longer than 6 months&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Canada</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/north-america/canada/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/north-america/canada/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="canada">
 Canada
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#canada">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Canada is a country located in North America, bordering the United States. In relative terms, obtaining a work permit in the United States is somewhat simpler. Quebec, a province in Canada, has a relatively different social environment, with French as its official language. Therefore, when considering opportunities in Quebec, one needs to take into account their abilities in multiple aspects.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="transgender-related-policies-and-resources">
 Transgender-Related Policies and Resources
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#transgender-related-policies-and-resources">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="healthcare-resources">
 Healthcare Resources
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#healthcare-resources">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Access to psychiatric and general prescription medications is somewhat strict, but gender-affirming healthcare is relatively comprehensive.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Finland</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/nordic/finland/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/nordic/finland/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="finland">
 Finland
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#finland">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Finland is a country located in Northern Europe, with Helsinki as its capital. Finland is a well-developed industrial country with major industries such as electronics, telecommunications, chemicals, wood processing and financial services.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Finland offers universal health insurance and free education (for its residents). Finland also has a high standard of living and welfare, and a relatively liberal immigration policy.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="transgender-related-resources">
 Transgender-related resources
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#transgender-related-resources">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>For more details before, during and after the application for a residence permit, there is an 
 &lt;a href="https://verbose.linzh.me/posts/2023-start-at-finland/">article&lt;/a> available here.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>France</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/france/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="france">
 France
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#france">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="study">
 Study
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#study">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="employment">
 Employment
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#employment">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="residence">
 Residence
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#residence">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>For proof of property, France has different requirements for different purposes in 
 &lt;a href="https://france-visas.gouv.fr/en/web/france-visas/ai-je-besoin-d-un-visa">France Visas&lt;/a>, so use the link above to see what you need for your purpose Use the link above to see the documents you need to prepare.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The criteria that can be used for reference are&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Proof of funds equivalent to at least 615 Euros per month (i.e. 7380 Euros/year).&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Proof of scholarship.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>or proof of deposit in a French bank account.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Or proof of financial support from a sponsor who must also prove an adequate, credible, and stable source of funding, accompanied by a copy of his or her identity document.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>After studying in France for at least two years, you can apply for French citizenship directly after graduation, or if you have lived in France for at least five years.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Germany</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/central-europe/germany/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/central-europe/germany/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="germany">
 Germany
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#germany">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="study">
 Study
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#study">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="application">
 Application
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#application">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Studying in Germany is mainly divided into undergraduate and master&amp;rsquo;s programs, as the requirements, preparation materials, and environment for each differ significantly. However, many resources are shared between undergraduate and master&amp;rsquo;s programs, so it is advisable to read both sections thoroughly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Due to frequent changes in educational policies, we recommend that you regularly check for updated policy information before and during your application. Additionally, standards and rules may vary significantly across different universities, so please develop a specific application plan and timeline based on the requirements of the university you are applying to.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Netherlands</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/thenetherlands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/thenetherlands/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="the-netherlands">
 The Netherlands
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#the-netherlands">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>The English proficiency rate is very high, and it has a relatively high income and lower taxes. At the same time, there is a high degree of social equality, and society is more friendly towards transgender individuals.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="transgender-resources-and-policies">
 Transgender Resources and Policies
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#transgender-resources-and-policies">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="medical-resources">
 Medical Resources
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#medical-resources">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>In the Netherlands, transgender individuals cannot decide autonomously whether to use hormones. They need to apply through the medical system. Even if they are on the waiting list, it usually takes one to two years from application to actually receiving Hormone Replacement Therapy (HRT) / Gender Affirming Hormone Treatment. If they were already using medication before, the probability of obtaining it can be increased, but it won&amp;rsquo;t reduce the waiting time.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Data Science</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/data-science/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/data-science/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="data-science">
 Data Science
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#data-science">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>With the development and application of artificial intelligence and data science, many companies such as Baidu and Huawei have also increased the number of competitions in this area and given generous prizes, etc.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="learning">
 Learning
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#learning">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If your college already offers related courses, such as machine learning and so on, you can try out and try hands-on practice in advance. But please don&amp;rsquo;t let the fact that many libraries have already implemented some of the functions prevent you from understanding the principles.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Denmark</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/nordic/denmark/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/nordic/denmark/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="denmark">
 Denmark
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#denmark">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="transgender-related-resources">
 Transgender-related resources
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#transgender-related-resources">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="organizations">
 Organizations
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#organizations">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
 &lt;a href="https://lgbt.dk/">LGBT Danmark&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
 &lt;a href="https://www.trans-aktion.dk/">TransAktion&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="study">
 Study
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#study">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="costs">
 Costs
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#costs">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>According to the 
 &lt;a href="https://studyindenmark.dk/">Study in Denmark&lt;/a>, non-EU/EEA students must provide sufficient funds to cover their tuition and living expenses. Proof of funds typically requires a bank statement demonstrating that you have enough funds to cover your tuition and living expenses.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For specific requirements, please refer to the website 
 &lt;a href="https://www.nyidanmark.dk/en-GB/You-want-to-apply/Study/Higher-education">for higher education&lt;/a> or 
 &lt;a href="https://www.nyidanmark.dk/en-GB/You-want-to-apply/PhD">PhD studies&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="employment">
 Employment
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#employment">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="residence">
 Residence
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#residence">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Denmark requires eight years of continuous residence in general, and four years in the shortest case. A Danish language proficiency test is required, and a naturalization exam is optional.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Japan</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/japan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/japan/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="japan">
 Japan
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#japan">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;blockquote class="book-hint info">
 &lt;p>&lt;strong>Content timeliness and accuracy remain to be seen&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Written by a contributor who is not a long-time resident of Japan, please find out more information from more sources.&lt;/p>

&lt;/blockquote>

&lt;p>Japanese society is built on a household registration structure, and thus transgenders who want to be recognized by society need to be able to have the conditions to obtain a wife/husband, i.e., they need to pass the external appearance, etc., in order to change their documents; and from a cultural perspective, they need to have the will to marry and have children. In addition, the overall social pressure in East Asia is relatively high, the whole social construction is also relatively traditional, and society on 
 &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Recognition_of_same-sex_unions_in_Japan">same-sex marriage&lt;/a> attitudes vary widely.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>New Zealand</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/oceania/newzealand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/oceania/newzealand/</guid><description/></item><item><title>University of Toronto</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/universities/northamerica/canada/uoft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/universities/northamerica/canada/uoft/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="university-of-toronto">
 University of Toronto
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#university-of-toronto">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="hrtgaht-starting-process">
 HRT/GAHT Starting Process
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#hrtgaht-starting-process">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>
 &lt;a href="https://mtf.wiki/zh-cn/docs/hrt/canada/uoft/">University of Toronto UofT - MtF.wiki&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Norway</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/nordic/norway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/nordic/norway/</guid><description/></item><item><title>China</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/china/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/asia/china/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="china">
 China
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#china">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;blockquote class="book-hint warning">
 &lt;strong>The overwhelming number of negative comments given by transgenders in this country, which may reflect a dangerous environment for transgenders in China.&lt;/strong>
&lt;/blockquote>

&lt;p>Even as a non-Chinese transgender, the society&amp;rsquo;s attitude towards you may still be bad in China, and you may still encounter many problems.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As a transgender exchange or degree student studying in China, you may still face significant difficulties, including but not limited to difficulty obtaining medication through official channels, only a small number of doctor doctors can prescribe a diagnosis of &amp;ldquo;易性症&amp;rdquo; (gender incongruence, but China uses an outdated name) that allows for more medical possibilities &lt;sup id="fnref:1">&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1&lt;/a>&lt;/sup>, very limited doctors who can prescribe HRT/GAHT &lt;sup id="fnref:2">&lt;a href="#fn:2" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">2&lt;/a>&lt;/sup>, lack of psychological support, widespread public attacks and institutional discrimination, and obstruction in academics and employment.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Iceland</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/nordic/iceland/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/nordic/iceland/</guid><description/></item><item><title>University of Waterloo</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/universities/northamerica/canada/uw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/universities/northamerica/canada/uw/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="university-of-waterloo">
 University of Waterloo
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#university-of-waterloo">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>
 &lt;a href="https://uwaterloo.ca/campus-wellness/health-services/student-medical-clinic/gender-affirming-care">Gender Affirming Care - University of Waterloo&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Network Security</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/network-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/network-security/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="network-security">
 Network Security
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#network-security">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>From the point of view of finding a job, cyber security, although you can find good working conditions and good pay, also because of the sensitivity of the industry, resulting in the actual choice is limited, after graduating from a foreign school, you may only be able to choose companies and other units.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Therefore, although it is not recommended as a preferred major, it is perfectly acceptable to consider if you like the profession.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Finland Transgender Newcomer's Guide</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/posts/starter-package-finland/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/posts/starter-package-finland/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="finland-transgender-newcomers-guide">
 Finland Transgender Newcomer&amp;rsquo;s Guide
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#finland-transgender-newcomers-guide">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Mainly for the Helsinki region. Last updated on August 5, 2023.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="before-arriving-in-finland">
 Before Arriving in Finland
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#before-arriving-in-finland">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In theory, do not bring any prescription medication into the Schengen Area without a prescription, and do not exceed one month for over-the-counter medications (check border control regulations). When you have a prescription, you are allowed to carry the medication indicated on the prescription, and the quantity should not exceed six months.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Commentary on Top 60-120 Liberal Arts Colleges</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/universities/northamerica/usa/60-120-ranking-liberal-arts-college/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/universities/northamerica/usa/60-120-ranking-liberal-arts-college/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="introduction-to-top-60-120-liberal-arts-colleges">
 Introduction to Top 60-120 Liberal Arts Colleges
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#introduction-to-top-60-120-liberal-arts-colleges">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>If the student population at the school has decreased in recent years (check the data), then it will be easier to apply for scholarships because they need your presence to polish their reputation. (After all, you are a good token.)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The pressure depends on your language proficiency and academic ability. If you have a near-native language level and all A&amp;rsquo;s, then there is no pressure. Most students at this level of school have poor academic performance, so rigor will be correspondingly lower.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Various facilities are complete. Generally, most places have unisex restrooms, and it&amp;rsquo;s okay to use the one you recognize. Other facilities are the same.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Support is hard to say. Most schools have psychological counseling but don&amp;rsquo;t expect too much. Don&amp;rsquo;t expect the school to help you when you encounter injustice. For reputation&amp;rsquo;s sake, the school generally supports the aggressor.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Staying in the US through work requires long-term planning.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Generally speaking, it is easier to apply for graduate school in liberal arts colleges.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>From Anonymous&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Guide to Name Change for Transgender Individuals in Finland</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/posts/change-name-finland/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/posts/change-name-finland/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="a-brief-guide-to-name-changes-for-transgender-individuals-in-finland">
 A Brief Guide to Name Changes for Transgender Individuals in Finland
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#a-brief-guide-to-name-changes-for-transgender-individuals-in-finland">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Name changes already made outside of Finland can be updated for free. Please refer to 
 &lt;a href="https://dvv.fi/en/registration-of-a-name-change-performed-abroad">this website&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="how-to-submit-an-application">
 How to Submit an Application
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#how-to-submit-an-application">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Note that if you wish to change your gender marker as well, refer to 
 &lt;a href="https://dvv.fi/en/confirmation-of-gender">Confirmation of gender - DVV&lt;/a>. After changing your gender, you can change your name for free. Remember, you must reconfirm within &lt;strong>30 days to 6 months&lt;/strong> after changing your gender marker.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>