<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>North America on Transgender University Guidance</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/north-america/</link><description>Recent content in North America on Transgender University Guidance</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/north-america/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>United States of America</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/north-america/usa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/north-america/usa/</guid><description>United States of America # The overwhelming number of negative comments given by transgenders in some states of this country, which may reflect a dangerous environment for transgenders in some states. The United States of America is currently the world&amp;rsquo;s leading country in science and technology and offers a relatively sophisticated system in many areas, including education and employment. Although the law prohibits discrimination against transgenders, transgenders are still treated unfairly in many ways, such as prejudice, violence, harassment, and some local laws.</description></item><item><title>Canada</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/north-america/canada/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/north-america/canada/</guid><description>Canada # Canada is a country located in North America, bordering the United States. In relative terms, obtaining a work permit in the United States is somewhat simpler. Quebec, a province in Canada, has a relatively different social environment, with French as its official language. Therefore, when considering opportunities in Quebec, one needs to take into account their abilities in multiple aspects.
Transgender-Related Policies and Resources # Healthcare Resources # Access to psychiatric and general prescription medications is somewhat strict, but gender-affirming healthcare is relatively comprehensive.</description></item></channel></rss>