<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Computer on Transgender University Guidance</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/</link><description>Recent content in Computer on Transgender University Guidance</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Computer Science and Technology</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/computer-science/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/computer-science/</guid><description>Computer Science and Technology # Contests # Algorithm competitions # Algorithm competitions require the design of algorithms to solve problems that are mathematically biased and receive time and language constraints.
Program development competitions # Compared to algorithm competitions, program development competitions are a bit longer. It is also not too restrictive on the developer&amp;rsquo;s technology stack, and the questions cover a wide range of aspects, so you can often find a topic that is relatively more suitable for you, and thus more flexible, but often less recognized than program development competitions.</description></item><item><title>Data Science</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/data-science/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/data-science/</guid><description>Data Science # With the development and application of artificial intelligence and data science, many companies such as Baidu and Huawei have also increased the number of competitions in this area and given generous prizes, etc.
Learning # If your college already offers related courses, such as machine learning and so on, you can try out and try hands-on practice in advance. But please don&amp;rsquo;t let the fact that many libraries have already implemented some of the functions prevent you from understanding the principles.</description></item><item><title>Network Security</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/network-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/preparation/computer/network-security/</guid><description>Network Security # From the point of view of finding a job, cyber security, although you can find good working conditions and good pay, but also because of the sensitivity of the industry, resulting in the actual choice is limited, after graduating from a foreign school, you may only be able to choose companies and other units.
Thus, although he is not recommended as a preferred major, it is perfectly acceptable to consider if you really like the profession.</description></item></channel></rss>