<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Western Europe on Transgender University Guidance</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/</link><description>Recent content in Western Europe on Transgender University Guidance</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>United Kingdom</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/uk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/uk/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="united-kingdom">
 United Kingdom
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#united-kingdom">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;blockquote class="book-hint warning">
 &lt;strong>The UK government has blacklisted over 50 countries for &amp;lsquo;making it too easy to change gender&amp;rsquo;, requiring any individual who moves from these blacklisted countries to the UK to reapply for a gender change in the UK. The blacklist includes countries like New Zealand and Belgium that recognize gender based on &amp;lsquo;self-declaration&amp;rsquo;. Please be aware of this condition when applying.&lt;/strong> [^1]
&lt;/blockquote>

&lt;h2 id="visa">
 Visa
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#visa">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The UK offers a work visa policy: if you graduate from a top 50 university in the world in your year of study, you will be eligible for a n-year work visa. So, if you graduated from a top 50 school in the world and you are not satisfied with a local career, you can take note of this information.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>France</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/france/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="france">
 France
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#france">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="study">
 Study
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#study">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="employment">
 Employment
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#employment">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="residence">
 Residence
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#residence">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>For proof of property, France has different requirements for different purposes in 
 &lt;a href="https://france-visas.gouv.fr/en/web/france-visas/ai-je-besoin-d-un-visa">France Visas&lt;/a>, so use the link above to see what you need for your purpose Use the link above to see the documents you need to prepare.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The criteria that can be used for reference are&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Proof of funds equivalent to at least 615 Euros per month (i.e. 7380 Euros/year).&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Proof of scholarship.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>or proof of deposit in a French bank account.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Or proof of financial support from a sponsor who must also prove an adequate, credible, and stable source of funding, accompanied by a copy of his or her identity document.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>After studying in France for at least two years, you can apply for French citizenship directly after graduation, or if you have lived in France for at least five years.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Netherlands</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/thenetherlands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/europe/western-europe/thenetherlands/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="the-netherlands">
 The Netherlands
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#the-netherlands">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>The English proficiency rate is very high, and it has a relatively high income and lower taxes. At the same time, there is a high degree of social equality, and society is more friendly towards transgender individuals.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="transgender-resources-and-policies">
 Transgender Resources and Policies
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#transgender-resources-and-policies">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="medical-resources">
 Medical Resources
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#medical-resources">#&lt;/a>
&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>In the Netherlands, transgender individuals cannot decide autonomously whether to use hormones. They need to apply through the medical system. Even if they are on the waiting list, it usually takes one to two years from application to actually receiving Hormone Replacement Therapy (HRT) / Gender Affirming Hormone Treatment. If they were already using medication before, the probability of obtaining it can be increased, but it won&amp;rsquo;t reduce the waiting time.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>