<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Central Europe on Transgender University Guidance</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Central/</link><description>Recent content in Central Europe on Transgender University Guidance</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Central/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Austria</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Central/Austria/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Central/Austria/</guid><description>Austria # Transgender-related resources # Organizations and institutions # Queer Base is an Austrian LGBTQ refugee organization aimed at providing shelter, support, and resources for LGBTQ refugees, as well as promoting the protection and advocacy of LGBTQ refugee rights. Transgender Medical Care # Questioning transgender medical care in German-speaking regions 1
Learning # First Steps to Studying in Austria
Details on visa application requirements and more
Third Country| Students with letter of admission| No mobility program | No agreement with higher education institution| Residence permit for students staying longer than 6 months</description></item><item><title>Germany</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Central/Germany/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Central/Germany/</guid><description>Germany # Study # Application # Studying in Germany is mainly divided into undergraduate and master&amp;rsquo;s programs, as the requirements, preparation materials, and environment for each differ significantly. However, many resources are shared between undergraduate and master&amp;rsquo;s programs, so it is advisable to read both sections thoroughly.
Due to frequent changes in educational policies, we recommend that you regularly check for updated policy information before and during your application. Additionally, standards and rules may vary significantly across different universities, so please develop a specific application plan and timeline based on the requirements of the university you are applying to.</description></item></channel></rss>