<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nordic on Transgender University Guidance</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Nordic/</link><description>Recent content in Nordic on Transgender University Guidance</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Nordic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sweden</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Nordic/Sweden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Nordic/Sweden/</guid><description>Sweden # Transgender Health Resources # In 2022, Sweden prohibits the provision of any hormone and hormone blockers to humans under the age of 18 for non-research purposes. And access to gender-affirming treatment is subject to psychiatric evaluation and must be lived for one year without any medical help to identify with the same gender. 1
As of February 1, 2023, Sweden is the only one of the five Nordic countries that has not passed the gender self-identification act.</description></item><item><title>Finland</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Nordic/Finland/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Nordic/Finland/</guid><description>Finland # Finland is a country located in Northern Europe, with Helsinki as its capital. Finland is a well-developed industrial country with major industries such as electronics, telecommunications, chemicals, wood processing and financial services.
Finland offers universal health insurance and free education (for its residents). Finland also has a high standard of living and welfare, and a relatively liberal immigration policy.
Transgender-related resources # For more details before, during and after the application for a residence permit, there is an article available here.</description></item><item><title>Denmark</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Nordic/Denmark/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Nordic/Denmark/</guid><description>Denmark # Transgender-related resources # Organizations # LGBT Danmark TransAktion Study # Costs # According to the Study in Denmark, non-EU/EEA students must provide sufficient funds to cover their tuition and living expenses. Proof of funds typically requires a bank statement demonstrating that you have enough funds to cover your tuition and living expenses.
For specific requirements, please refer to the website for higher education or PhD studies.
Employment # Residence # Denmark requires eight years of continuous residence in general, and four years in the shortest case.</description></item><item><title>Norway</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Nordic/Norway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Nordic/Norway/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Iceland</title><link>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Nordic/Iceland/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uniguide.transacademic.org/docs/countries/Europe/Nordic/Iceland/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>